[
  { 
    "question": "Ogoshi", 
    "answer":   "Large Hip Throw"
  },
  { 
    "question": "Seoi Otoshi", 
    "answer":   "Drop Knee Shoulder Throw"
  },
  { 
    "question": "Osoto Gari", 
    "answer":   "Large Outer Reap"
  },
  { 
    "question": "Ippon Seoi Nage", 
    "answer":   "One Arm Shoulder Throw"
  },
  { 
    "question": "Morote Gari", 
    "answer":   "Double Leg Takedown or 2 Handed Reap"
  },
  { 
    "question": "Ouchi Gari", 
    "answer":   "Large Inner Reap"
  },
  { 
    "question": "Osoto Maki Komi", 
    "answer":   "Large Outer Wrapping Throw"
  },
  { 
    "question": "Kesa Gatame", 
    "answer":   "Scarf' Hold"
  },
  { 
    "question": "Yooko Shiho Gatame", 
    "answer":   "Side Mount / Side Locking Four Corner Hold"
  },
  { 
    "question": "Kata Gatame", 
    "answer":   "Shoulder Hold / Arm Triange"
  },
  { 
    "question": "Kami Shiho Gatame", 
    "answer":   "Upper 4 Corner Hold / North South"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yusei gachi", 
    "answer":   "Decision Win!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hiki Wake", 
    "answer":   "Draw Match!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Waza Ari Awasete Ippon", 
    "answer":   "A full point by adding two waza ari scores"
  },
  {
    "question": "Newaza", 
    "answer":   "Techniques from a supine position"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shime/Jime", 
    "answer":   "Choke"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ju", 
    "answer":   "The principal of gentleness or giving way"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do", 
    "answer":   "Way of life"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jujitsu", 
    "answer":   "Gentle arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tokui waza", 
    "answer":   "Favorite technique"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bushido", 
    "answer":   "Way of the warrior"
  },
  {
    "question": "Budo", 
    "answer":   "Martial Arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kyu", 
    "answer":   "Class of belt ranks in Judo below Black Belt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dan", 
    "answer":   "Step of Degree in the Black Belt ranks"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uchi Komi", 
    "answer":   "Repetiition attack practice without throwing, done with partner"
  }




]
